

MUHAMMAD NASRULLOH

Fullstack Developer

About Me

Hello there! I am Muhammad Nasrulloh, a passionate Fullstack Web Developer with a creative spirit and a strong drive to build exceptional digital experiences.



+62 8123 234 0020 (WA / Phone)



muhammadnasrulloh.id@ amail.com



Sawahan, Mojosari, Mojokerto

LANGUAGE

- Indonesian
- English (basic)

EXPERTISE

- Fullstack Developer
- Backend Develoepr
- Frontend Developer
- Web Designer (Basic)

EXPERIENCE

Backend Developer Remote - Whitebox.id 2023 - 2024

I've been a Backend developer handling pla-to.com (LMS) & pesen.id (Ordering Application) server-side tasks like Database management, Redis caching and API development, and collaborating with Front-End teams.

Web Developer (Internships) SMKN 1 Pugging - Indonesia 2023

For 6 months I interned as a web developer at a high school, namely SMKN 1 Pugging. While there, I was with 7 people who were part of 3 developer teams. My team created a warehouse goods management application.

Freelance Web Developer.

Remote

2022 - NOW

I am a freelance web developer with experience working on various platforms such as Fiverr and Sribulancer. I specialize in delivering high-quality, custom web solutions tailored to clients' needs, Like Scripting, build mockup and web pages.

EDUCATION

Politeknik Elektronika Negeri Surabaya

D3 Teknik Informatika 2020-2023

MAN 1 MOJOKERTO

Religion Department 2017-2020

SKILLS SUMMARY

Data Modeling

81%

Javascript/Typescript

95%